Hello everyone, today we will give you a comparison of
two very good funds of the large cap category, which are
such potential
blue chip drives.
Very good. At the
end of the subscribe, we will also
tell you which is our favorite fund.
First, let's talk about the launches.
India's top fund companies
come in the launch category and
invest in this type of company. You should invest only in this
disgusting
subscribe and
subscribe. I
welcome you to this channel. On this channel, we
regularly share information regarding insurance and investment. If you have any
question, you
can ask us in the comment section, you can call, you
can WhatsApp and if you
like our comparison, then like the video and
definitely subscribe to the channel. Let's
start the comparison. First of all, let's
talk about the basic details. Both are open
end schemes. One is of Principal MC
Company while the other is of Mirae Asset & C
Company. The date of purchase of both the funds is
January 2018. Benchmark  Both are
front running phases. Your mercy petition
is per hectare whereas Mirae asset class has
0 crores per hectare. Expense ratio
of ICC potential is 1.00 whereas Mirae asset
class is Chapter 06. There is no entry load
in both the funds. Exit load is 1%. If
you withdraw the money before one year,
then the minimum SIP investment
in such condition is ₹1 and minimum long term is ₹10 which is the minimum investment for the
North Indian fund. If
you are a student and have
this portion, then you
can invest with minimum amount and take it from the market. If you
subscribe, then
in the last such fund it has
given a return of 10, whereas in this one
it has
given a return of six. Click on the
subscribe button and
subscribe. If you have
subscribed to the channel, then
you can see that you have
set the subscription for long term. Talking about lump sum
investment, if you had invested
1000 rupees in such potential bluechip one year ago, then today  Its value is
12th versus
subscribe
if you
subscribe more than 100 then its
900 to
subscribe
40 If we
talk about the fund's portfolio then such
chip holdings
come to 94574, 0.43 per cent is in debt and
4.8 per cent is in 10 market
capitalization In this one, 79.61 per cent is invested in large cap,
5.7 per cent in midcap and
0.4 per cent in small cap,
total number of stocks is 6th If we talk about
Mirae Asset Large Cap's portfolio in such Brinjal Bluechip Fund, then
this point
is 1980 and in this there is an investment of 1.2 per cent market
subscribe
subscribe 6 and total
number is 66 To
boost the subscribe button, if we
talk about turnover then in this there is an
investment of 9.73 per cent in ICICI Bank,
7.7 per cent in HDFC Bank and
6.7 per cent in Infosys  Axis Bank is a strong investment
in the phase of entry of 5.30 points.
Talking about Mirae Asset Class 11 Chapter Note,
Infosys has around 600,
State Bank of India has
subscribed sectors. Talking about the same,
360 Smart Technology
Sure
Subscribe Mirae Asset Last Step's
top-5 sectors, Sign in
More Technology Se Z
Quote 61 Automobiles 5.5 Tractor
Investment So you can see that both the
friends were
subscribed. Talking about Mirwaiz fund manager, he had
almost 10 years of experience and
manages important things and manages 3000
crores. Secondly, while
subscribing to Meghwal,
talking about the fund manager of ICC Potential, it is managed by 3 fund managers.
Firstly, fund manager Ansh Dawa
please
subscribes for
430.80 crores. Secondly, the one who
manages Hansa Skin, one
person
manages 3000 crores. Thirdly,
fund manager
subscribes and  If you
use 10 crore, you can see
that both have experienced subscribers from their managers,
which are very famous. If we talk about the
setting of the rating agency for both, then the
subscriber is 16 and Iusan Crandon
is known for chapters. Here my
tab screen
quickly beta of this potential
from 08 2010
shows how much risk someone is
taking, how much time is there and the
subscriber is considered, but here the beta
[music]
subscribe is
1.79
subscribe -0.5,
that someone gives obscene,
now we can adjust this and here the
juice of such potential, which is fresh, is quite good
comparatively, my tab is large cap, as
we told you in the last of the video, we will
tell you that our fabric is
both are looking good, but if you
use both, then our front ICC is
maintained very well, we keep
getting some subscribers, so please like our channel and
subscribe, thank you for
watching.